<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>easy on cloetpatrick.eu</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/tags/easy/</link><description>Recent content in easy on cloetpatrick.eu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>cloetpatrick.eu</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 16:20:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cloetpatrick.eu/tags/easy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Recipe of Perfect Easy Kanto-Style Sakura Mochi Using an Electric Griddle</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/126-recipe-of-perfect-easy-kanto-style-sakura-mochi-using-an-electric-griddle/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/126-recipe-of-perfect-easy-kanto-style-sakura-mochi-using-an-electric-griddle/</guid><description>Before you jump to Easy Kanto-Style Sakura Mochi Using an Electric Griddle recipe, you may want to read this short interesting healthy tips about Ways To Live Green Plus Conserve Money In The Kitchen.It was not that long ago that hippies and tree huggers were the only ones to show concern concerning the well-being of the ecosystem. That&amp;rsquo;s a thing of the past now, with everyone being aware of the problems besetting the planet and the shared burden we have for turning things around.</description></item><item><title>How to Make Favorite Easy crock pot Mac~n~Cheese</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/128-how-to-make-favorite-easy-crock-pot-macncheese/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2020 07:46:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/128-how-to-make-favorite-easy-crock-pot-macncheese/</guid><description>Before you jump to Easy crock pot Mac~n~Cheese recipe, you may want to read this short interesting healthy tips about Green Living In The Kitchen Can save you Money.Until fairly recently any person who indicated concern about the wreckage of the environment raised skeptical eyebrows. Those days are over, and it seems we all realize our role in stopping and conceivably reversing the damage being done to our planet. Unless everyone begins to start living much more environmentally friendly we won&amp;rsquo;t be able to fix the problems of the environment.</description></item><item><title>Simple Way to Prepare Quick Easy and Lovely Chewy Tender Heart-Shaped Dango (Dumplings)</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/129-simple-way-to-prepare-quick-easy-and-lovely-chewy-tender-heart-shaped-dango-dumplings/</link><pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2020 02:15:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/129-simple-way-to-prepare-quick-easy-and-lovely-chewy-tender-heart-shaped-dango-dumplings/</guid><description>Before you jump to Easy and Lovely Chewy Tender Heart-Shaped Dango (Dumplings) recipe, you may want to read this short interesting healthy tips about Easy Ways to Get Healthy.You already realize that, to achieve true health, your diet needs to be sensible and wholesome and you need to get a good amount of exercise. Sadly, there isn&amp;rsquo;t constantly enough time or energy for us to really do the things we need to do.</description></item><item><title>Step-by-Step Guide to Make Super Quick Homemade Easy Tuna Carbonara</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/127-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-easy-tuna-carbonara/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 01:11:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/127-step-by-step-guide-to-make-super-quick-homemade-easy-tuna-carbonara/</guid><description>Before you jump to Easy Tuna Carbonara recipe, you may want to read this short interesting healthy tips about The Simple Ways to Be Healthy.You already know that, to achieve true health, your diet needs to be sensible and wholesome and you need to get a good amount of exercise. The unfortunate thing is that, at the end of the day, we don&amp;rsquo;t always have the time or energy required for a healthy lifestyle.</description></item><item><title>Easiest Way to Prepare Perfect Easy Marble Cake #HealthyBakingContest</title><link>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/127-easiest-way-to-prepare-perfect-easy-marble-cake-healthybakingcontest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 08:00:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cloetpatrick.eu/post/127-easiest-way-to-prepare-perfect-easy-marble-cake-healthybakingcontest/</guid><description>Before you jump to Easy Marble Cake #HealthyBakingContest recipe, you may want to read this short interesting healthy tips about The Basics of Being Healthy.Everyone knows that in order to truly be healthy you need to eat a nutritious and balanced diet and get a proper amount of exercise. Sadly, there isn&amp;rsquo;t always enough time or energy for us to really do the things we need to do. When our work day is done, most people do not prefer to go to the gym.</description></item></channel></rss>